<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>每日阅读 on nonacosa's Blog</title><link>https://blog.env.wtf/categories/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E9%98%85%E8%AF%BB/</link><description>Recent content in 每日阅读 on nonacosa's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:55:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.env.wtf/categories/%E6%AF%8F%E6%97%A5%E9%98%85%E8%AF%BB/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is the frequency illusion</title><link>https://blog.env.wtf/p/what-is-the-frequency-illusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:55:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://blog.env.wtf/p/what-is-the-frequency-illusion/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://blog.env.wtf/p/what-is-the-frequency-illusion/media/s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com_2022-12-22_17_47_12.png" alt="Featured image of post What is the frequency illusion" />&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/asCTUscO_Ec"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>Have you ever bean shopping for a car, a phone, a watch, or&lt;span style="background-color: rgba(251, 243, 219, 1);">a pair of&lt;/span>sunglass&lt;span style="color: rgba(217, 115, 13, 1);">es&lt;/span>and, once you settle on the model you want, you start seeing it everywhere? There’s a name for thatphenomenon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The term thefrequency illusionwas coined by Stanford and Ohio Statelinguisticsprofessor Arnold Zwicky. The basic idea is that, once you become consciouslyaware ofsomething, you start to notice it everywhere, the reality is, obviously, that those things were always there; you just never noticed them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We’re drowning inbits.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The frequency illusionis related tomotivation because you can’t be motivated todo something you aren’t aware of.&lt;span style="color: rgba(68, 131, 97, 1);"> &lt;em>&lt;strong>If you never consciously think about something, there’s no way you can actually do anything about it.&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> &lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The frequency illusion&lt;span style="background-color: rgba(253, 235, 236, 1);">illustrates&lt;/span>how your subconscious mind can recognize much more of what’s in your environment than your conscious mind perceives.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Depending on which study you read, the amount of incoming information that yourconsciousmin can process is somewhere in the range of 60 bits per seconds.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I won’t get into details of whatconstitutesa “bit” in this context, because it’s not relevant to this discussion&lt;span style="color: rgba(68, 131, 97, 1);"> &lt;em>&lt;strong>. The point is simply that your subconscious mind has&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color: rgba(68, 131, 97, 1);"> &lt;em>&lt;strong>vastly&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> &lt;/span>&lt;span style="color: rgba(68, 131, 97, 1);"> &lt;em>&lt;strong>more capacity to notice things in your environment than your conscious mind does.&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> &lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Putting the frequency illusion to work for you&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So, how can youcounteractthismonopolizationof your conscious awareness? You can use the frequency illusion to youradvantageto increase your motivation by“priming” your brainto notice the kinds of things that are important to you and that you want to focus on.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The key is to train your subconscious mind what things are important to you, so it can let you know when those “opportunities” arise.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>&lt;strong>actually absolutely&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="actually--vs--certainly">&lt;em>&lt;strong>actually VS certainly&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Actually&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;certainly&amp;rdquo; are both adverbs that can be used to express certainty or to emphasize a point. However, they are used in slightly different ways.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Actually&amp;rdquo; is used to indicate that something is true or real, often in contrast to what was previously thought or believed. For example:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;I thought the store closed at 9pm, but actually it closes at 10pm.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Certainly&amp;rdquo; is used to express strong assurance or certainty. It can be used to affirm a statement or to agree with someone. For example:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Will you be able to come to the meeting on Wednesday? - Certainly, I&amp;rsquo;ll be there.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m certain that he will be able to fix the problem.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In general, &amp;ldquo;actually&amp;rdquo; is used to provide information that may be surprising or unexpected, while &amp;ldquo;certainly&amp;rdquo; is used to express strong confidence or assurance.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="demonstrates-vs-illustrates">&lt;em>&lt;strong>demonstrates VS illustrates&lt;/strong>&lt;/em>&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Demonstrates 和 illustrates 都是动词，表示证明或表现的意思。两者的意思有很大的重叠，但是在某些情况下，两者有一些微小的区别。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Demonstrates 强调表现出来的过程，指在特定的情况下，通过动作或行为来证明或表明某件事情。例如，&amp;ldquo;The scientist demonstrated the experiment to the class&amp;rdquo;（科学家向班里展示了这个实验）。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Illustrates 则指通过图画、图表或其他形式的表示来阐述或说明某件事情。例如，&amp;ldquo;The teacher illustrated the concept with a diagram&amp;rdquo;（老师用图表来解释这个概念）。&lt;/p>
&lt;p>总的来说，demonstrates 常用于指人的动作或行为，而 illustrates 常用于指静态的图画或图表。但是这两个词也可以互换使用，具体使用哪个单词取决于您想要传达的意思以及上下文。&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>